extremeoverclocking.com 2019-11-05

# EXTREME Overclocking | Tweaking Enthusiast PC Hardware Product Reviews And News

### Our Commitment To Privacy:

Your privacy is important to us. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect on various parts of our website, in our forum, and when you signup for a contest. EXTREME Overclocking will never sell or give your personal information to advertisers, sponsors, or any third party company. 

### Registration:

You may be required to register for a member account (free, of course) to access specific areas of our site or to get involved in our community (forums). We require all new registrations to be authenticated by you. We do this by sending you an email after you have registered to "activate" your account on EXTREME Overclocking. This helps to cut down on spam and users that try to create more than one account on EXTREME Overclocking. We may require that you provide your email that was assigned to you by your ISP (Internet Service Provider) when registering for your EXTREME Overclocking account. However, your email will NEVER be given or sold to advertisers, sponsors, or any other 3rd party companies. Again, we do this to cut down on users who try to signup for multiple accounts. You will never receive any further emails from EXTREME Overclocking (Exceptions include the one time activation email, and an occasional email to verify your email account is still valid).

### Mailing List:

The EXTREME Overclocking mailing lists are a way for us to communicate with our audience by offering news, reviews, and other relevant information. Our mailing list readers will be the first to know when we release new reviews, how-to guides, and other big site news. All that is required by you, is a valid email address. Unlike our registration process that may require your ISP email address, our mailing list will accept any valid email address. Like our registration process, you will receive an email from us that verifies your email and your intent to join the mailing list. EXTREME Overclocking will never sell or give your personal information to advertisers, sponsors, or any third party company.

### Cookies:

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. **Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site**. We use both session id cookies and persistent cookies. For the session id cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. This type of cookie is used mostly in our forum. When you sign in with your user id and password you can click the button that says "Remember me". The next time you visit the forum, you will automatically be logged in, thanks to cookies. By setting a cookie on our site, users would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If users reject the cookie, they may still use our site, but would have to enter their password and login over and over. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site, like our forum. Persistent cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. Advertisers can not personally contact you in anyway whatsoever. Advertisers nor any other 3rd party has any information that can identify you personally.

### Third Party Advertising:

The ads appearing on EXTREME Overclocking are delivered to users by our ad-server and our advertising partners. Information about users who visit EXTREME Overclocking, such as number of times they have viewed an ad (but not user name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to users on this site. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by EXTREME Overclocking only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers, affiliates, or 3rd party sites.

### Links:

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, EXTREME Overclocking, are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.

### Surveys & Contests:

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and email address). User submitted information may be forwarded to the sponsor of the contest for reasons that shall be disclosed in the rules and regulations of any applicable contest. Anonymous survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. User's personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties unless we give prior choice.

### Security:

This web site takes every precaution to protect our user's information. When users submit sensitive information via the web site, their information is protected both online and off-line On our site we have programs implemented to protect your email address in our forums. Even if you choose to "show" your email address in our forums, initial contact must be submitted through an online form, so other users will not know your actual email address unless you reply to them. On the Internet there are "spam bots", which surf the Internet and collect every email address they find and place them in a database, then they send junk email to all of these users. We take every effort possible to block these "spam bots" and filter / remove any publicly posted email addresses.

### Notification of Changes:

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

### Contact Information:

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please go to our [contacts page](http://www.extremeoverclocking.com/contact_info.php).
